(Sheldon:)Would you call that moss green
or forest green?
HOWARD:
Look at this. Everyone went chimp.
RAJESH:
I'd like to point out, I voted for orangutan...
(Raj:)...but you shouted me down.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
LEONARD: Oh, hi, Penny.
- Hey, where are you?
(Leonard(running down stairs):)I'm at work.
(Penny:)You sound funny.
Oh, I'm in a radiation suit.
(Leonard:)- What's up?
- Yeah, well, I'm at work too.
(Penny:)And you'll never guess who's here
infecting my entire station.
(Leonard(To Howard and Raj):)Sheldon's at the Cheesecake Factory.
- Just tell him to go home.
- Well, he won't leave.
(Penny:)He says he's afraid he'll pass out on the
bus and someone will harvest his organs.
(Leonard(To Howard and Raj):)He's paranoid
and he's established a nest.